[{"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "SERVO"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "\u22644.0\"", "Display Resolution": "854x480", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "IPS", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "2MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "0.3MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "1000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G", "NFC": "no", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "no", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "<3000 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,FCC", "Item Condition": "New", "MTK Model": "MT6580", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "SAMSUNG"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "Other"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "5.8", "Display Resolution": "960x540", "Screen Refresh Rate": "Other", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "TFT", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "8MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "Other"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "2600 mAh", "Battery Type": "Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Micro USB", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Dedicated slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "no", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Photograph Phone"}, "Other": {"Color": "White/Black", "Biometrics Technology": "no", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11n 2.4 GHz,802.11b/g,802.11a", "Samsung Model": "Galaxy Mega 5 8", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "<3000 mAh", "Video recording resolution": "FullHD (1080p) 30 fps", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "Refurbished", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "Language": "Polish,German,French,Norwegian,Turkish,ITALIAN,Spanish,Portuguese,Russian,English,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Built in radiator": "no"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "realme"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.67''", "Display Resolution": "2400x1080", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Fullview Display", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "2MP,8MP,50MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "4500", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "SuperCharge", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Face Recognition", "realme model": "Realme GT Neo 3", "Design": "BAR", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "NONE", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,French,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "XIAOMI"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.67''", "Display Resolution": "3200x1440", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "OLED", "Screen Type": "Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "48Mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "20MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5500", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Other", "Charging Power": "67W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "5 G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Photograph Phone,5G Mobile Phone"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted", "Design": "BAR", "Xiaomi Model": "Redmi K60E", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Video recording resolution": "4K (2160p) 30 fps", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "Used", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Built in radiator": "no"}}, {}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "OUKITEL"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.8\"", "Display Resolution": "720x1600", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "50MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "5mp"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5150", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Other": {"Item Condition": "New", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "OUKITEL Model": "C33", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Origin": "Mainland China"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "BLACKVIEW"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.21", "Display Resolution": "1520X720", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "LCD", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "4", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "13MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "5mp"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "4200", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Micro USB", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Dedicated slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "no"}, "Other": {"FDD spec": "B1/B3/B7/B8/B20", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11n 2.4GHz/5 GHz", "Design": "BAR", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Apple"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "APPLE"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.1", "Display Resolution": "1792\u00d7828", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "IPS", "Screen Type": "Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "12MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "12MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "3110", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "YES", "Fast Charging": "Other", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Linghting", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "IOS"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Face Recognition", "Apple Model": "iPhone 11 4GB 64GB", "Design": "BAR", "Origin": "US(Origin)", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "Used", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "XIAOMI"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "Other"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "8.03", "Display Resolution": "2160x1916", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "AMOLED", "Screen Type": "Folded Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "50MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "20MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "4800", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "YES", "Fast Charging": "SuperCharge", "Charging Power": "67W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Not supported", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Others"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Optical Stabilization,Photograph Phone,Fast Charging Phone"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted", "Design": "BAR", "Xiaomi Model": "Xiaomi Mix Fold 3", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English"}}, {}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "XIAOMI"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.39''", "Display Resolution": "2340x1080", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "3"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "20MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "\u224848MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "4000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Quick Charge 4.0+", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Xiaomi Model": "k20", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "Used", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Cubot"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.583", "Display Resolution": "2408x1080", "Screen Refresh Rate": "60Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Full Screen,Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "48Mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "24MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "4500-5999", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Other", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Photograph Phone"}, "Other": {"Face ID": "No", "Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted", "Design": "BAR", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,FCC,RoHS,WEEE", "Item Condition": "New", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "BLACKVIEW"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.5", "Display Resolution": "1600x720", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen,Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "12MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "8MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5080", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Other": {"Item Condition": "New", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Origin": "Mainland China"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Apple"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "APPLE"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "5.5", "Display Resolution": "1080x1920", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "12MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "5mp"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "2750", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Linghting", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Not supported", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "IOS"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES"}, "Other": {"Apple Model": "iPhone 6S Plus", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,FCC,RoHS", "Item Condition": "Used", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Cubot"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "2.5", "Display Resolution": "480 * 320", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "5mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "3MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "1000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "no", "Design": "BAR", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Apple"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "APPLE"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.55", "Display Resolution": "1242x2688", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "12MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "12MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "3969", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "YES", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Linghting", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "IOS"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "4G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES"}, "Other": {"Apple Model": "iPhone 11 Pro Max", "Biometrics Technology": "Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "3000-3500 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "Refurbished", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Built in radiator": "YES"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "SOYES"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "\u22644.0\"", "Display Resolution": "480x320", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "LCD", "Screen Type": "Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "2MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "\u22641MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "1000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Others"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "no"}, "Other": {"3G": "WCDMA/B1/B5", "Biometrics Technology": "no", "Design": "BAR", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "XIAOMI"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.67", "Display Resolution": "2400x1080", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "AMOLED", "Screen Type": "Full Screen,Fullview Display", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "100MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "33W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Others"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "no", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Xiaomi Model": "Redmi Note 13", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Apple"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "APPLE"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "5.5", "Display Resolution": "1080x1920", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "2"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "12MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "Other"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "2900", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Linghting", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "IOS"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "4G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "<3000 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "Used", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "Apple Model": "7 plus", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Built in radiator": "YES"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "XIAOMI"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.58", "Display Resolution": "2408x1080", "Screen Refresh Rate": "90Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "50MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "5mp"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "18W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Photograph Phone,Fast Charging Phone"}, "Other": {"Weight": "201g", "Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Xiaomi Model": "M5", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "XIAOMI"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "qualcomm"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.67", "Display Resolution": "1080x2400", "Screen Refresh Rate": "60Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "Super AMOLED", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "4", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "13MP,2MP,8MP,\u224864MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "20MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "4400", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Not supported", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G,5 G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Photograph Phone,5G Mobile Phone,Fast Charging Phone"}, "Other": {"Color": "Black/White/Blue/Purple", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11ac,802.11n 2.4GHz/5 GHz,802.11b/g,802.11a", "Design": "BAR", "Xiaomi Model": "Redmi K30 Pro Zoom", "Battery Capacity Range": "3500-4499 mAh", "Video recording resolution": "FullHD (1080p) 30 fps,FullHD (1080p) 240 fps,4K (2160p) 30 fps,4K (2160p) 60 fps,8K (4320p) 24 fps,8K (4320p) 30 fps,FullHD (1080p) 60 fps,FullHD (1080p) 120 fps", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "Used", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Qualcomm Model": "Snapdragon 865", "Built in radiator": "no"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "SAMSUNG"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "qualcomm"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "4.5", "Display Resolution": "960x540", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "Super AMOLED", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "8MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "5mp"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "1900", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Micro USB", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Dedicated slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "4G", "NFC": "no", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "no", "Samsung Model": "Galaxy A3", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "<3000 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "Refurbished", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Qualcomm Model": "Snapdragon 410", "Built in radiator": "YES"}}, {}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Motorola"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "qualcomm"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "5.5", "Display Resolution": "1920x1080", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "AMOLED", "Screen Type": "Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "20MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "3300", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Dash Charge", "Charging Power": "20W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Not supported", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "NONE", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Qualcomm Model": "Snapdragon 835"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "BlackBerry"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "qualcomm"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "3.5", "Display Resolution": "720 x 720 pixels", "Screen Refresh Rate": "144Hz", "Touch Screen": "No", "Screen Material": "LCD", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "8MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "2MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "2515 mAh battery", "Battery Type": "Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Micro USB", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Dedicated slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Other Smartphone OS"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "no", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Photograph Phone"}, "Other": {"Blackberry Model": "Q20(CLASSIC)", "Biometrics Technology": "no", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11n 2.4 GHz,802.11b/g,802.11a", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "<3000 mAh", "Video recording resolution": "FullHD (1080p) 30 fps", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "Used", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Korean,Arabic", "Built in radiator": "no"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Cubot"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.95''", "Display Resolution": "1640x720", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "IPS", "Screen Type": "Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "48Mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Other", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Dedicated slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Photograph Phone"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "ULEFONE"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.52\"", "Display Resolution": "720 x 1600 HD+", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "13MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "5mp"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "4500mah", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "no"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Apple"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "APPLE"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "4.7", "Display Resolution": "1334x750", "Screen Refresh Rate": "60Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "LCD", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "12MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "7MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "1960", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Linghting", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Not supported", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "IOS"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "no"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Photograph Phone"}, "Other": {"Color": "Golden/Silver/Rose", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Apple Model": "iPhone 7", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11ac,802.11n 2.4 GHz,802.11b/g,802.11a", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "<3000 mAh", "Video recording resolution": "FullHD (1080p) 30 fps,4K (2160p) 30 fps,FullHD (1080p) 60 fps,FullHD (1080p) 120 fps", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "NONE", "Item Condition": "Used", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Built in radiator": "no"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Apple"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "APPLE"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.1", "Display Resolution": "1792\u00d7828", "Screen Refresh Rate": "60Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "LCD", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "12MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "12MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "3110", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Linghting", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Not supported", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "IOS"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Photograph Phone,Fast Charging Phone"}, "Other": {"Color": "White/Green/Red/Black etc", "Biometrics Technology": "Face Recognition", "Apple Model": "iPhone 11 4GB 64GB", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11ac,802.11n 2.4 GHz,802.11b/g,802.11a", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "<3000 mAh", "Video recording resolution": "FullHD (1080p) 30 fps,4K (2160p) 30 fps,4K (2160p) 60 fps,FullHD (1080p) 60 fps,FullHD (1080p) 120 fps", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "Used", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Built in radiator": "no"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "XIAOMI"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.73\u201c", "Display Resolution": "3200x1440", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Curved Screen,Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "50MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "32MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "4600", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "YES", "Fast Charging": "SuperCharge", "Charging Power": "120W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "MIUI 13"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "In-Screen Fingerprint Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Xiaomi Model": "xiaomi 12", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "NONE", "Item Condition": "Used", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "UNIWA"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.3", "Display Resolution": "1080*2340px", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "24MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "5mp"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Optical Stabilization,Photograph Phone,Sports Phone"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "ULEFONE"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "5.45''", "Display Resolution": "1440x720", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "LCD", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "20MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "5mp"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5180", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES"}, "Other": {"4G FDD-LTE": "1700(B4)MHz, 1800(B3)MHz, 1900(B2)MHz, 2100(B1)MHz, 2600(B7)MHz", "Biometrics Technology": "Face Recognition", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11ac,802.11n 2.4GHz/5 GHz,802.11n 2.4 GHz,802.11b/g,802.11a", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "French,German,Russian,English,ITALIAN,Spanish,Portuguese"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "BlackBerry"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "3.2", "Display Resolution": "480X360", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "TFT", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "NONE"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "5mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "None Front Camera"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "600", "Battery Type": "Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Micro USB", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Dedicated slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "BlackBerry"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "Other,3G,2G", "NFC": "no", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "no", "Blackberry Model": "9380", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "<3000 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "Used", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "HTC"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "5.5", "Display Resolution": "1280x720", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "LCD", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "13MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "5mp"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "2600", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Micro USB", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Other": {"RAM": "1.5GB", "Biometrics Technology": "no", "HTC Model": "DESIRE 816", "Design": "BAR", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "NONE", "Item Condition": "Used", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Norwegian,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "XIAOMI"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.55", "Display Resolution": "2400x1080", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Curved Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "50MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "32MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "4500", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "YES", "Fast Charging": "Quick Charge 4.0", "Charging Power": "67W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G,5 G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Photograph Phone,5G Mobile Phone,Fast Charging Phone"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Design": "Flip", "Xiaomi Model": "CIVI 3", "Battery Capacity Range": "3500-4499 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English"}}, {}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Hotwav"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.53inch", "Display Resolution": "1600x720", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "20MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "5mp"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "15000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "18W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Sports Phone"}, "Other": {"4G": "B1/B3/B5/B7/B8/B19/B20", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Rear-mounted", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "7500+ mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "UMIDIGI"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.52", "Display Resolution": "1600*720", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "13MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "5mp"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5150", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "no"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted", "Design": "BAR", "": "none", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "SAMSUNG"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.5", "Display Resolution": "720x1600", "Screen Refresh Rate": "60Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "LCD", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "4", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "48Mp,2MP,8MP,5mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "13MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "4500", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Quick Charge 2.0", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card,1 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G,5 G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Photograph Phone,5G Mobile Phone"}, "Other": {"Color": "White/Black/Blue", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11ac,802.11n 2.4 GHz,802.11b/g,802.11a", "Samsung Model": "A32-5G", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "3500-4499 mAh", "Video recording resolution": "FullHD (1080p) 30 fps,4K (2160p) 30 fps,FullHD (1080p) 120 fps", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "Refurbished", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "MTK Model": "Dimensity 720 MT6853", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Built in radiator": "no"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "IIIF150"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.78", "Display Resolution": "2460*1080", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Fullview Display", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "200MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "32MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "15000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "SuperCharge", "Charging Power": "65W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES"}, "Other": {"Weight": "465g", "Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted,Face Recognition", "Design": "Flip", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "MIL-STD-810G": "YES", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,Turkish,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Built in radiator": "YES"}}, {}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "ULEFONE"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "5.5", "Display Resolution": "1440*720", "Screen Refresh Rate": "60Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "13MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "5mp"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Micro USB", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Sports Phone"}, "Other": {"phone free shipping": "portable", "Biometrics Technology": "Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,FCC", "Item Condition": "New", "MTK Model": "Helio A25", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "LG"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "qualcomm"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "5.7", "Display Resolution": "2560x1440", "Screen Refresh Rate": "60Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "LCD", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "8MP,16MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "5mp"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "2750", "Battery Type": "Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Other", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Dedicated slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "no", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Photograph Phone"}, "Other": {"Color": "Black/Silver/Pink", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11ac,802.11n 2.4 GHz,802.11b/g,802.11a", "Design": "BAR", "LG Model": "V20", "Battery Capacity Range": "<3000 mAh", "Video recording resolution": "FullHD (1080p) 30 fps,4K (2160p) 30 fps,HD (720p) 120 fps", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "NONE", "Item Condition": "Refurbished", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "Language": "English,Russian,French,Spanish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Qualcomm Model": "Snapdragon 820", "Built in radiator": "no"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "LG"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "qualcomm"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.8\"", "Display Resolution": "2460x1080", "Screen Refresh Rate": "60Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "AMOLED", "Screen Type": "Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "48Mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "4300", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "YES", "Fast Charging": "Quick Charge 4.0+", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES"}, "Other": {"Water-Proof": "Not Support", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "LG Model": "G9", "Battery Capacity Range": "3500-4499 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "NONE", "Item Condition": "Used", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "UMIDIGI"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.53inch", "Display Resolution": "1600x720", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "LCD", "Screen Type": "Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "16MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "8MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5150", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "no"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11ax", "Design": "BAR", "": "295369929", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "MTK Model": "Helio G25", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "unihertz"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "4.2", "Display Resolution": "768x1280", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "IPS", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "48Mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "8MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "4100", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,FCC", "Item Condition": "New", "MTK Model": "Helio P70", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Japanese"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "DOOGEE"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.58\u201d", "Display Resolution": "2408x1080", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "IPS", "Screen Type": "Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "200MP,24MP,16MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "32MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "10800", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "33W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "5 G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted", "Design": "BAR", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Doogee Model": "V30 Pro"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "realme"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.74 inches", "Display Resolution": "1600x720", "Screen Refresh Rate": "90Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "50MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "5mp"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5000mAh", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "SuperVOOC", "Charging Power": "33W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Dedicated slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "no", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Photograph Phone,Fast Charging Phone,Sports Phone"}, "Other": {"Processor": "Octa-core", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "realme model": "realme C51", "Design": "BAR", "Video recording resolution": "FullHD (1080p) 30 fps,HD (720p) 30 fps", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "ZTE"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "qualcomm"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.67''", "Display Resolution": "2400x1080", "Screen Refresh Rate": "144Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "AMOLED", "Screen Type": "Full Screen,Fullview Display", "Rear Camera Quantity": "4", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "\u2248108MP,8MP,2MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition,In-Screen Fingerprint Recognition", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11n 2.4GHz/5 GHz", "Design": "BAR", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "NONE", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English"}}, {}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "OUKITEL"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.58\u201d", "Display Resolution": "2408x1080 FHD+", "Screen Refresh Rate": "60Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "LCD", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "2"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "20MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "20MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "10000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Other", "Charging Power": "18W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Dedicated slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Optical Stabilization"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "OUKITEL Model": "WP26", "Battery Capacity Range": "7500+ mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "MIL-STD-810G": "YES", "MTK Model": "Helio P90", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "ROG"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.78", "Display Resolution": "1080x2340", "Screen Refresh Rate": "165Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "AMOLED", "Screen Type": "Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "13MP,\u224864MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "24MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "6000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Quick Charge 4.0", "Charging Power": "65W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Not supported", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Optical Stabilization,Game Phone,Photograph Phone,5G Mobile Phone,Fast Charging Phone"}, "Other": {"MTK model": "MediaTek Dimensity 9000+", "Biometrics Technology": "In-Screen Fingerprint Recognition,Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11n 2.4GHz/5 GHz", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "6000-7499mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,FCC", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Huawei"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.1", "Display Resolution": "1080 x 2340", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "OLED", "Screen Type": "Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "\u224840MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "32MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "3650", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "22.5W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Huawei Model": "P30"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "SOYES"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "\u22644.0\"", "Display Resolution": "854x480", "Screen Refresh Rate": "Other", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "IPS", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "13MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "5mp"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "1900", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Photograph Phone,Sports Phone"}, "Other": {"Features 2": "Face ID Fingerprint Unlock Phone", "Biometrics Technology": "Face Recognition,Rear-mounted", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11n 2.4GHz/5 GHz,802.11n 2.4 GHz,802.11b/g,802.11a", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "<3000 mAh", "Video recording resolution": "HD (720p) 30 fps", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,FCC", "Item Condition": "New", "MTK Model": "MT6737", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {}]